[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 5]
[Big Ocean Motorcycle Workshop]
Really?
So this big treasure is mine now?
Anyway, I'm going abroad,
and I can't take it with me.
You have to treat it well from now on.
Don't worry.
I absolutely won't mistreat it.
There's one more thing.
Do me a favor when you have time.
Regarding that batch of fish
in the school pool,
please deliver them with the tank
to someone for me.
That isn't a problem at all. To whom?
Zhou Wan.
Zhou Wan?
But I'm not close to her.
Aren't you close to Gu Meng?
Bro.
Since when?
Why didn't I know?
What do you mean by since when?
You didn't wear your school uniform
at the school gate,
and your name was recorded by her
more than 50 times.
How can you say you're not close to her?
I-If you put it that way,
I'll give it a try.
Take good care of it.
Don't worry.
Jiang Fan asked me out?
Yeah.
He was being all mysterious.
What does that mean?
Why did he ask me out?
He said
he wanted to give something to you.
Just go, Wan.
I've already promised to help him.
Never mind.
I happen to have something
which I want Jiang Fan to deliver for me.
Did he say where we should meet?
Yes, let me check.
I found it. I'll send it to you.
Hello?
Xixiao.
Why is this fish tank still here?
Where else should it be?
Didn't I tell you to find time
to move it and give it to Zhou Wan?
D-Didn't you want Zhou Wan
to move it directly?
I...
Alright. Seriously,
I have nothing to say to you.
Just come and move it away quickly. Okay?
Why are you here?
Jiang Fan asked me to come here.
He said he wanted to
give something to me.
I didn't know you were here.
Do you usually live here?
Where I live is none of your business.
Never mind.
There was a miscommunication.
It's fine.
I actually have something for you.
I've washed your coat.
Last time,
I didn't know you would come to school,
so I didn't get a chance
to return it to you.
Thank you.
I heard you helped me cover up
my plan of going abroad
in front of the director.
We're even now.
Xixiao.
I'm sorry. Okay?
What's more, well...
You shouldn't hit a smiling person.
You didn't make it clear back then.
-It's not entirely my fault, right?
-I told you.
Ms. Zhou is here, too.
This is perfect.
Come on.
Since you two are both here,
let's get this straight. Okay?
By talking face-to-face,
there won't be any misunderstandings.
Alright?
Come on. Please have a seat.
Now we can hear
your opinions
regarding the custody
of this fish tank.
Who wants to start first?
Didn't I tell you to find time
to move
this fish tank and give it to Zhou Wan?
I misunderstood what you said.
This fish tank is so big
that I don't have room for it in my house.
Since this fish tank is so big,
how can I take it with me
while taking a plane?
That's right.
It's not allowed to take it to a plane.
We saved these fish together.
Logically speaking,
we should each
take half the responsibility.
But there's only this one tank,
and it's too late
to buy a new one now.
Then what should we do?
How about we put it in your house?
In my house?
I agree.
I agree, too.
I...
Well...
My house?
Today is the first day of the 2016
national college entrance exam.
To create a safe, quiet and smooth
exam environment
for all candidates,
here's a friendly reminder from
the Pingchuan Public Security Bureau
and the Traffic Police Detachment.
Candidates,
please check in advance whether you've
brought your admission tickets,
ID cards and stationery.
In case of traffic jams or emergencies,
please call 122 immediately
or seek help
from on-duty police officers on the roads.
We will provide
emergency escort services.
Do you need to bring
a few more pencils?
No need.
The first test only
has over 10 fill-in-the-blank questions.
Here.
It's not allowed
to take these things, either.
Are you wearing your watch?
You'll need it to check the time.
It's not allowed to wear a watch.
It's not allowed to wear a watch, either?
Gosh.
I didn't say you couldn't wear it.
Look how nervous I am.
People might think I'm taking the exam.
What's wrong with your hand?
I-I-It's fine.
The skin is just peeling, isn't it?
Didn't you tell me to sunbathe?
It was caused by the sunbath.
When did it happen?
J-Just yesterday.
Didn't I just go sunbathing yesterday?
Wait for me.
Hurry up.
Only after I escort you there
can I feel relieved.
Walk slowly when you go down the stairs.
Hurry up!
It's a call from the school.
They said he didn't attend
t-the college entrance exam.
Where is he?
I've asked around.
He bought a flight ticket to go abroad.
He should be boarding soon.
Put his mother's house
up for sale.
Then update him on the news.
Got it.
[National College Entrance Examination]
[May You Succeed
in the College Entrance Exam!]
[Good Luck
with the College Entrance Exam!]
[College Entrance Exam, We're Coming!]
[2016
National College Entrance Examination]
[Pingchuan Experimental High School
Test Center]
There are quite many people
wearing Qipaos.
-Yeah.
-Obviously...
They all want good luck
and a successful start.
Why didn't I think of
wearing a Qipao?
If one prepares well before the exam,
he can evem take the exam in pajamas.
You're always such a eloquent girl.
Now that there are not many people here,
go inside at once.
Your forehead is covered with sweat.
Don't wait for me.
Go home now, okay?
Alright.
Do you want me to pick you up?
If you want to
change into a Qipao to pick me up,
that's okay, too.
Go!
-Bye bye.
-Good luck.
I'm leaving.
Stay safe.
[No Honking in the Test Center Area]
Bye bye!
Don't be nervous.
[Rules for Candidates]
Good luck!
[Int'l & Hong Kong/Macau/Taiwan Departures]
Hello.
[Rules for Candidates]
Okay.
Come this way, please.
Go inside.
Ma'am, are you okay? Ma'am!
Ma'am! Ma'am!
-Ma'am!
-Are you okay?
Okay.
-What's wrong?
-Be careful.
-Ma'am.
Ma'am, are you okay?
-What's wrong, Ma'am?
-Ma'am.
What's wrong?
Grandma!
[Rules for Candidates]
[Candidate Waiting Area]
Grandma!
Someone fainted.
[Int'l & Hong Kong/Macau/Taiwan Departures]
[In Surgery]
Xixiao.
Lu Zhongyue
wants to sell your mom's house.
Do you know that?
[Int'l & Hong Kong/Macau/Taiwan Departures]
[In Surgery]
[Discussion Room]
Dr. Chen, how is my grandma?
She's out of danger now.
But after the surgery, she still
needs to stay in the hospital
for observation and treatment.
[Discussion Room]
Why did she suddenly have a heart attack?
Diabetic patients
actually have a higher incidence
of cardiovascular diseases.
What's more, your grandma is old now
with several complications,
and uremia is just one of them.
But don't worry.
Trust us
as we will do our best to treat her.
How about this?
I'll go give the nurses
some instructions first.
I'll talk to you later
about the postoperative recovery.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, by the way,
what about your exam tomorrow?
It's fine.
I'll take the exam next year.
I'll go home and pack some clothes
for her to change into.
I'll be here early tomorrow morning.
[Admission Ticket]
No need to move all the four paintings.
Regarding the Four Seasons series,
j-just move that
s-s-summer one.
Not this one.
I-It's that one.
The one with the woman in a red dress
and the white horse.
The one painted in
r-r-red and green colors.
Keep it down.
Hurry! Hurry up!
Watch your steps. W-Watch...
What are you doing?
No, Xixiao!
Xixiao, this is Mr. Lu's idea.
-Get up!
-No!
We have an event these few days
and need to use that painting.
Well, Xixiao...
Don't be impulsive!
Don't worry.
We'll return it when we finish using it.
W-We're leaving.
Go... Go get some rest.
Go get some rest.
♪ People ask me how to heal ♪
♪ But what's the point
of questioning and leaving? ♪
♪ Naiveness is always used
in the wrong place ♪
♪ Sadly, I didn't notice anything ♪
♪ The panic in your steps ♪
♪ Is the symphony named betrayal ♪
♪ Your silent answer ♪
♪ Is the confusion
that pushed me to the valley bottom ♪
♪ Me and myself ♪
♪ The unsettled self ♪
♪ Dancing at night ♪
♪ I want to calm my broken heart ♪
♪ Looking at myself ♪
♪ With those traces of being teased ♪
♪ I want to show my love
but I always step on the glass ♪
[Wish You Success in the Exam
with a New Start and a Promising Future!]
♪ If promises can't be broken ♪
♪ If true love can't be abandoned ♪
♪ Me and myself ♪
♪ The unsettled self ♪
[Wish You Success in the Exam
with a New Start and a Promising Future!]
♪ Dancing at night ♪
♪ I want to calm my broken heart ♪
♪ Looking at myself ♪
♪ I want to show my love
but I always step on the glass ♪
♪ If promises can't be broken ♪
♪ If true love can't be abandoned ♪
♪ I'm the only one left to heal myself ♪
[Urgent Sale: A Villa in Shanhai Huafu]
[Located on a sunny slope,
with a south-facing layout]
Your dad's tactic is really despicable.
He put your mom's old house
up for sale.
Alright. It's your misjudgment, too.
You should just stay there
for a few more days.
If a student
doesn't take the college entrance exam,
his family will definitely be notified.
Don't you know that?
I'll live there from now on.
I've changed the lock, too.
I'd like to see who dares to sell it
or go inside.
Let me tell you.
If you keep hiding,
it isn't a good solution.
In my opinion,
you should talk to your dad properly.
In your opinion...
Can you just
stop talking about your opinion?
Ping.
You've hired a new clerk, haven't you?
Where is she?
Right! She's in that room.
I've told her to practice first.
She's also from your school.
I think you know each other.
She's my niece.
There are so many people in our school.
There aren't many of them I truly know.
Not necessarily.
The top scorer
of the college entrance exam in our city
is also from your school.
-His name is Zhou...
-Zhou Jiayi.
He always ranked third.
That's right. His score is 705 points.
Very impressive.
Why isn't it Zhou Wan?
Why are you still thinking about her?
She must have messed up her exam
as soon as you left.
I asked for an imported steering damper.
What kind of garbage did you give me?
Why didn't you say so just now?
Why did you wait
till you finished trying it?
How would I know if I didn't try it?
Are you finding fault with me on purpose?
Are you making trouble?
It's a problem
about your service attitude.
Stop!
What's wrong?
She gave me the wrong component.
What do you think is the problem?
Gu Meng?
Why are you here?
See?
I said you two knew each other.
So she's your niece?
Yeah.
My issue hasn't been solved yet.
I'll find... find another one for you.
Steering damper!
Do you know a lot
about fixing motorcycles?
-Don't argue with him.
-It's none of your business.
I remember
your family runs real estate business.
-When did you change to fix motorcycles?
-What do you know?
What are you showing off for?
I'm a customer.
Stop arguing.
Why are you making trouble here?
-Xixiao!
-What's your purpose?
Xixiao, Xixiao, Xixiao.
It's you again.
I was wondering why this motorcycle
looked so familiar.
Honestly,
your motorcycle is quite nice indeed.
This whole...
Did I let you touch my motorcycle?
S-S-S-Stop arguing.
Did I let you touch it?
Xixiao!
I know you.
Lu Zhongyue's son, Lu Xixiao.
Even your dad has to beg my family.
What does that have to do with me?
Since you're so defiant,
and we both have the hobby
of riding motorcycles,
do you dare to race against me?
If you win,
I'll smash my motorcycle.
But if you lose,
you'll have to kneel down
and apologize to me.
Do you dare, Lu Xixiao?
Good luck!
[Pingchuan Station, Starting Line]
Lu Xixiao, good luck!
[Racing Cup,
Pingchuan Station, Starting Line]
Good luck!
-Good luck!
-You must defeat him!
Xixiao.
I know you can win.
But you should still stay safe.
Good luck! Good luck!
Lu Xixiao.
Have you figured out
how you're going to lose?
Stop pretending.
You'll have to kneel if you lose.
What a brat.
Good luck!
[Racing Cup, Pingchuan Station]
Lu Xixiao, good luck!
Why can He Wenhui ride so fast?
After He Wenhui's motorcycle was refitted,
its performance became really good.
In the first section,
Xixiao might be at a disadvantage.
Then he's doomed.
Of course not.
Though the components are not good enough,
his skills can make up for it.
I'm sure Xixiao can do this.
I just took a look at
He Wenhui's motorcycle.
All its components have been
replaced with the latest imported models.
All the motorcycle repair shops
in Pingchuan
couldn't even gather those components,
let alone using them on one motorcycle.
That costs a lot of money.
Then what's the point of having a race?
Just give him the "Filthy Rich Man" award.
Racing isn't that simple.
Xixiao's motorcycle has also
been tuned by himself bit by bit.
This haphazardly assembled motorcycle
is no match for his.
What's more,
Xixiao's racing skills
are also better than his.
That's right.
After watching it for a while, we'll know
He Wenhui's true ability.
Xixiao has passed through the bridge.
Next, there will be a long straightaway.
On this straightaway,
He Wenhui can utilize
his maximum performance advantage.
An advantage again?
Uncle, can't you say something positive?
Calm down.
When they passed through
the bridge just now,
I observed it carefully.
He Wenhui's cornering skills
are far inferior to Xixiao's.
As long as Xixiao firmly keeps up
with He Wenhui on the straightaway,
he'll have a great chance later.
After the long straightaway,
it'll be the S-bend
which Xixiao is best at.
In this field, no one
has ever been able to break his record.
Xixiao is invincible
on this part of the racing track.
-Come on, Lu Xixiao!
-He's going to overtake him.
If I'm not mistaken,
in the second lap,
the gap between them
will narrow even more.
Really?
Xixiao has maintained
the motorcycle's performance
very well.
And his handling of the cornering lines
is more accurate.
He will slowly narrow
the previous gap
and then wait for a chance
to overtake He Wenhui.
The longer it takes,
the better it'll be for him.
Look! Lu Xixiao is only a little bit
behind him on the straightaway.
He's playing dirty tricks!
You can't afford to lose, huh?
How shameless!
What He Wenhui just did
was definitely deliberate.
If Xixiao hadn't reacted quickly,
he would have crashed.
Come on, Lu Xixiao!
Don't lose to
that poser who plays dirty tricks!
Don't worry.
On the bend, Lu Xixiao
can still narrow the gap.
Look! I told you so!
The gap between Xixiao and him
has narrowed again.
I was right, huh?
Come on!
Though He Wenhui's motorcycle is fast,
his own
aggressive driving style
is too rough for the motorcycle.
His cornering speed
will get slower and slower
as the race goes on.
Lu Xixiao won't let go
of this opportunity.
On the S-bend,
he will narrow the gap again.
In the end, he'll wait for a chance
to overtake him.
The gap between them is very small.
Xixiao has done very well
on the straightaways.
[Finishing Line]
Whether Xixiao can win
depends on the last bend
of the third lap,
which is right here.
They're coming.
This very bend of the last lap!
This bend is the most important!
Xixiao!
He won!
[Finishing Line]
[Racing Cup, Pingchuan Station]
He won!
Awesome!
So great!
Amazing!
[A Sure Win]
Just some basic operations.
He was just lucky this time.
Admit defeat and keep your promise!
Someone is going to kneel.
Lu Xixiao! You played dirty tricks, huh?
-Who played dirty tricks?
-What?
You can't afford to lose, huh?
Will you do it yourself
or should we help you?
Who dares to touch it?
Ping!
Lu Xixiao!
You can't afford to lose, huh?
If you can't afford to lose,
don't come out to play anymore.
Let's go!
-Let's go!
What a sore loser.
So what if you're rich?
He defeated you.
Lu Xixiao.
How about coming to our shop?
Just wait and see.
I can even give you a discount.
She's coming.
Little liar.
Oh, she has quite a temper.
She has quite a temper.
I thought
we'd have a top scorer
among our tenants.
-But you didn't even enter the test center.
-If I become the top scorer,
will you stop coming to collect rent?
Of course not.
I can't make things difficult for myself
just because you're having a hard time.
It's time to pay the rent. Pay up.
Didn't I pay it last time?
Last time was last time.
This time is this time.
That's right.
Besides,
if you don't pay us the rent,
what will we eat and use?
Hurry up. Give us the money.
Give us the money.
Really?
I can also go ask your boss
what exactly is going on.
Are you threatening me?
Fine. I can't explain it clearly to you.
Fen knows it.
I'll go talk to Fen.
You're such a drag.
Hello, Wenhui.
What are your instructions?
Lu Xixiao?
Keep an eye on her.
What's wrong? You and he...
Alright. I'll be right there.
This isn't over.
Brat.
You messed with the wrong person.
I'm sorry,
but I was asked to do this.
Speaking of He Wenhui,
this is all that he's capable of, huh?
How stubborn.
I like tough guys.
Hit him.
That's right. Thanks for your help.
Please come as soon as possible.
Okay. We'll go there right away.
Please ensure your own safety.
Wan!
Where are you going?
Get on quickly. I'll take you there.
Meng,
lend me your scooter.
Y-You'll ride it?
Yes, I'll ride it.
Thanks.
B-B-Be careful.
Be careful not to break my scooter, too.
Take him away.
Stop her!
Stop her now!
Get on!
♪ We've both held fragility ♪
♪ Talked through our misery ♪
♪ This time
I'm holding tight to your will ♪
♪ Lighting up all the sparks ♪
♪ Hoping it doesn't slip away ♪
♪ In this boring universe ♪
♪ Drifting day by day ♪
♪ Until the day I choose
to break away for you ♪
♪ And that's enough to do ♪
♪ Falling into your tenderness ♪
Hurry! The police are coming.
Zhou Wan?
Let's go.
The police... The police are coming!
♪ Slowly being saved ♪
Bro, hurry up! Let's go!
Turn your face around.
Let me give your wound
a simple treatment first.
You'd better go to the hospital.
Don't get the wound wet,
or it will get inflamed easily.
Alright. That's almost done, huh?
This isn't fully attached to your wound.
Wait a moment.
Then I'll... I'll get going now.
The noodles are ready!
The noodles are ready.
Why don't you have some noodles
before you go?
I don't want to owe anyone favors.
This meal is on me.
Let's go.
-You...
You can speak first.
Didn't you pass the language test?
Why didn't you go?
Then let me ask another question.
Why did you get into a fight?
Because they were looking for trouble.
If you don't believe it, just forget it.
Does it matter if I believe it or not?
Zhou Wan.
You were the one who offered to
be my tutor at first.
And now you're the one who has been
hiding from me for no reason.
If you really don't want to
get involved in my matters
or have anything to do with me,
why did you get to know me?
Not everyone can
live as they please.
And not everyone can
do whatever they want.
Today, I just happened to see you.
I was being nosy.
Don't take it to heart.
I didn't mean anything else.
♪ I will keep this frozen heart ♪
♪ I think someone will accept it ♪
♪ In my broken heart ♪
Even if it was a coincidence,
can't you regard it
as fate?
♪ Someone's gonna fix it ♪
♪ It's just that I'm unforgivable ♪
♪ Self-reflection in your heart ♪
♪ Being ignorant doesn't mean ♪
♪ I can do whatever I want ♪
♪ I seem to have never ♪
♪ Closed the sunroof ♪
♪ Telling you how the sky above the roof ♪
♪ Is full of stars ♪
[Big Ocean Motorcycle Workshop]
Meng.
I'm here to return the scooter.
Wan.
Don't worry.
The police have taken them away
for interrogation.
Those several hooligans
have all been arrested.
It's good that we are safe.
I'll thank you properly another day.
I'm leaving now.
You're leaving so soon?
Bye bye.
Gu Meng.
Thank you for lending her the scooter.
Don't mention it.
I'm glad I could help.
What's going on between them?
It's none of your business.
This isn't a water tank.
Why are you adding water to it?
Who did you fight with?
I just bumped into something.
You bumped into something?
Why do I find it so hard
to believe your words?
Is it because of Miss Straight-A?
You're blaming Zhou Wan again?
Whenever something happens,
you always blame Zhou Wan.
Something so serious
has happened in her family.
She doesn't have time to...
What happened in her family?
Tell me.
I also have no idea,
but her grandma is hospitalized and...
What?
What did she say?
She said her grandma...
She missed the college entrance exam
because her grandma was hospitalized.
And she can't afford the medical bills.
She's having quite a hard time.
You can't even understand that?
You could even understand that?
[Reception Area
of Dialysis Treatment Room 1]
Are you okay today? Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
I'm just a little tired.
[Reception Area
of Dialysis Treatment Room 1]
Let me do it.
Okay.
The patient is old,
so her recovery process
will be rather slow.
Make sure she gets enough rest.
Okay.
As for today's bill,
I'll go pay it.
The bill?
Didn't you
already pay it today?
I'll accept the drink,
but I really can't let you
pay the medical bills for me.
I'm very grateful to you.
I know this money
might just be a small amount to you.
But I'm an adult now.
I'm an able-bodied person.
I can make money by myself.
I've already transferred it to you
on WeChat.
You must accept it.
When we were
at the noodle restaurant yesterday,
why didn't you tell me?
This is not some good news.
Why would I talk about it?
I transferred the money to you
not because I pitied you.
Previously,
when you offered to be my tutor,
wasn't it also for
your grandma's medical bills?
-Now, isn't this a good way to...
-When I was your tutor,
you and I had an employment relationship.
S-S-So...
I earned the money
to pay the medical bills.
That was different.
Now, as your friend,
can I help you?
Ma'am, give me an ice cream cone.
Okay.
Do you want one?
Thanks.
I'll pay.
How much is it?
Five yuan.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thanks.
[Heartbeat Player]
Excuse me, are you hiring?
Have you played this claw machine before?
That claw machine has a mechanism.
Two people already
caught dolls from it this morning.
I think it's very hard
for you to catch one now.
Then you probably haven't heard
how good I am.
I'm just afraid you'll waste your money.
You're afraid I'll waste my money?
But why do I feel this money
was well spent?
So you really managed to catch one?
Do you like it?
It's for you.
It looks quite like you, too.
I'm Zhou Wan.
What?
♪ Give me some candlelight ♪
It's for you. Take it.
♪ Let it illuminate his face ♪
♪ if your voice is hoarse ♪
This necklace...
♪ It'll lead to more imaginations ♪
It's for you.
It's for me?
♪ The warm night breeze ♪
Let me ask you.
♪ Has filled the corridor ♪
Are we still friends?
♪ Wet clothes ♪
♪ Flowing waves ♪
♪ Don't think about tomorrow ♪
This goes with my bow and arrow,
doesn't it?
♪ Look away in the next second ♪
Is that so?
♪ Tell a long joke ♪
It's just a coincidence.
♪ Fill up all the cracks ♪
♪ I don't want to live a wandering life ♪
♪ I don't care what belief he has ♪
Enough.
Don't ask so many questions.
♪ What does the world
have to do with me? ♪
I'll accept the necklace.
But this Kobito is too ugly.
-What?
-It doesn't look like me at all.
♪ It's getting late ♪
It looks quite like you.
Take a look by yourself.
It's like looking in a mirror.
♪ His obsession ♪
What's wrong?
Someone broke into my house.
Do you need help?
Do you want me to go with you?
Okay.
This is the place I saw last time.
This is my mom's house.
Mr. Li.
I guarantee
you'll absolutely be satisfied
after seeing this house.
There are many other people
who are on the waiting list
to see this house.
The owner
is already waiting for you inside.
Who is this?
Mrs. Lu!
Mr. Li is here to see the house.
Hello. Come in.
Be careful.
Thanks for your hard work, Li.
It's my duty.
Come in.
Are you selling the house?
It won't be sold. Let's go.
Don't be impulsive.
We'll run into them if we go inside.
Then what should we do?
Are there any other entrances?
Over there. Let's go.
Mr. Li, this way, please.
The area of this house
is about
580 square meters in total.
What's your plan?
I haven't come up with a plan yet.
Well, didn't you confidently say
that you had a plan?
This is your house, not mine.
I'm looking right now, aren't I?
If you like anything,
you can keep it.
Cut the crap.
Do you think I lack the money?
You're right.
Mr. Li,
we are sincere.